{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which song in rapper Kanye West&#039;s album &quot;The Life of Pablo&quot; features Rihanna?","correct_answer":"Famous","incorrect_answers":["Wolves","Ultralight Beam","Highlights"]},{"category":"Vehicles","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Jaguar Cars was previously owned by which car manfacturer?","correct_answer":"Ford","incorrect_answers":["Chrysler","General Motors","Fiat"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What was the world&#039;s first handheld game device?","correct_answer":"Mattel Auto Race","incorrect_answers":["Game Boy","Microvision","Game &amp; Watch"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Celebrities","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In what year did &quot;Bob Ross&quot; die?","correct_answer":"1995","incorrect_answers":["1986","1989","1997"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What are the names of the Ice Climbers in the video game Ice Climber?","correct_answer":"Popo and Nana","incorrect_answers":["Popo and Nina","Papi and Nana","Papi and Nina"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which director directed the movie &quot;Pan&#039;s Labyrinth&quot;?","correct_answer":"Guillermo Del Toro","incorrect_answers":["Alfonso Cuar&oacute;n","Alejandro Gonz&aacute;lez I&ntilde;&aacute;rritu"," Alejandro Jodorowsky"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In AMC&#039;s TV Series &quot;The Walking Dead&quot; what are &quot;Zombies&quot; referred to as?","correct_answer":"Walkers","incorrect_answers":["Creepers","Maggots","Hell Pigs"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Before it&#039;s redesign of the company logo in the year 2000, which 3D shape is NOT represented in the Electronic Arts logo?","correct_answer":"Cylinder","incorrect_answers":["Pyramid","Cube","Sphere"]},{"category":"Sports","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the name of Manchester United&#039;s home stadium?","correct_answer":"Old Trafford","incorrect_answers":["Anfield","City of Manchester Stadium","St James Park"]}]}